A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Peace and Social Justice Division (PSJ), Governance and Civil Society, Program Officer, Office Files of Michael Lipsky FA595
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1965-2003; 6
  - Documentation Memos - Amy Nogle for State Fiscal Analysis Initiative and govWorks, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 428)
  - Galing Pook Awards Program Assessment, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - Grant Files for American Renewal, 1999-2001 (Box 38, Folder 430)
  - Portland Fund for Civic Innovation, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 431)
  - Reference Materials Held to Return Calls, 1999-2001 (Box 38, Folder 432)
  - Trip Itineraries, Emails, and Faxes Awaiting Response, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 433)
  - Innovations Survey, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 434)
  - Active File - Institute for Women's Policy Research, Fiscal Policy Institute, Reports, Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 435)
  - London World Wide Philanthropy (WWP) Meeting, 1997-1998 (Box 39, Folder 436)
  - The State of Democracy: Project Proposal, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 437)
  - State of the States, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 438)
  - The Innovations in Government Programs: Documentation, Evaluation, and Dissemination, Judith Tendler, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 439)
  - Correspondence and Reports from Russell Dalton, University of California, Irvine, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 440)
  - The World in Pieces: Culture and Politics at the End of the Century, Clifford Geertz, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 441)
  - Unconventional Wisdom: The Ideas, Dissents, and Legacy of John Kenneth Galbraith, International Center for Global Communications Foundation - Proposal, 2001 March 1 (Box 39, Folder 442)
  - Northwest Federation of Community Organizations, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 443)
  - Workshop Invitation from Janet Weiss, University of Michigan, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 444)
  - Memo - Recommendations for National and Community Service at the Foundation, 2000 January (Box 39, Folder 445)
  - Committee on Indigenous Peoples, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 446)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives (CPA) - Summit on the States, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 447)
  - Letter from Ashley O. Thrift, North Carolina Partnership for Children, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 448)
  - Honoring Nations: Honoring Contributions in the Governance of American Indian Nations - 1999 High Honors and Honors Recipients (Box 39, Folder 449)
  - International Institute for Democracy and Electoral Assistance (IDEA), 1999 (Box 39, Folder 450)
  - Clipping - Sexual Assault Nurse Examiner (SANE) Program, 1999 April 20 (Box 39, Folder 451)
  - Philanthropy and Trust in Government, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 452)
  - Remarks by Michael Lipsky for the First Impumelelo Awards, 1999 December 8 (Box 39, Folder 453)
  - Advocacy Institute - New Leaders Program Team, undated (Box 39, Folder 454)
  - Center on Budget and Policy Procedures, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 455)
  - Oganizational Profile Book, WAJF Tax Shift Meeting, Chevy Chase, Maryland, 1999 October 20-22 (Box 39, Folder 456)
  - Program Officer Memo - Michael Lipsky - Government Performance and Accountability, 1999 June 16 (Box 39, Folder 457)
  - Animating Democracy Initiative, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 458)
  - Citizen Participation and Implications for Program Development in Chile, Colombia, Argentina and Peru, Ramon Borges Mendez, 1997-1999 (Box 39, Folder 459)
  - Esperanza Unida, Inc., 1999 (Box 39, Folder 460)
  - California Budget Project, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 461)
  - Reinventing Government, Frank J. Thompson and Norma M. Riccucci, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 462)
  - Innovations in Government Awards Program - Background Paper, undated (Box 39, Folder 463)
  - Indiana University - The Center on Congress, Lee Hamilton Proposal, 1999 March (Box 39, Folder 464)
  - Honoring Nations: Honoring Contributions in the Governance of American Indian Nations, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 465)
  - Programa Ciudadania y Gestion Local, Chile - Applications and Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 466)
  - Eliminating Barriers to Voting: Election Day Registration Symposium - Invitation, 2001 October (Box 40, Folder 467)
  - Peace and Social Justice Trustees Trip to the South - Alabama, 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 468)
  - Privatization of Human Services in New York City: Some Examples and Lessons, James A. Krauskopf, 1995 October 24 (Box 40, Folder 469)
  - The Production and Use of Fiscal Analysis by Non-Governmental Organizations in the American States: The Case of New York's Fiscal Policy Institute and the Distributional Impact of Governor George Pataki's Tax Reduction Plan, Frank J. Mauro, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 470)
  - Speaker's Notes for R. Kadalie, Lead Respondent to Peter Spink on the Rights Approach to Local Governance Reform, The Context of the Impumelelo Award Programme in South Africa, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 471)
  - Improving Local Governance: A Conference of the Ford Foundation hosted by Honoring Nations, St. Paul, Minnesota - Agendas and Participants Lists, 2000 November 12-16 (Box 40, Folder 472)
  - Livable Wage Movement, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 473)
    Sponsored by the Ford Foundation
    Participants: Washington Association of Churches, Washington Citizen Action, Washington State Labor Council, AFL-CIO
  - Washington Trip File, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 474)
  - Report and Roundtable Discussion on American Democracy Prepared for the Joyce Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 40, Folder 475-476)
  - IBM Partnership File, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 477)
  - Correspondence and Reports, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 478, Box 41, Folder 479)
  - Good Sewers Cheap?: Agency-Customer Interactions in Low-Cost Urban Sanitation in Brazil, Gabrielle Watson, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 480)
    The World Bank, Water and Sanitation Division
  - Fulbright U.S. Student Program - Fulbright and Related Grants for Graduate Study and Research Abroad, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 481)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives, 2001 June 16 (Box 41, Folder 482)
  - Council for Excellence in Government - Proposal, 2001 October (Box 41, Folder 483)
  - Monthly Lunch - Michael Lipsky and Urvashi Vaid, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 484)
  - Trustee Peace and Social Justice Committee, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 485)
  - International Civil Society, Budget Work Support Project - Advisory Group Meeting, 2002 April 29-30 (Box 41, Folder 486)
  - National Civic League, 2001 November (Box 41, Folder 487)
  - Leadership for a Changing World Awards Celebration, 2001 October 25 (Box 41, Folder 488)
  - Meeting with Bill Rowe and Kim Carton, North Carolina Justice and Community Development Center, undated (Box 41, Folder 489)
  - Bob Fulkerson, Progressive Leadership Alliance of Nevada, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 490)
  - Economic and Social Policy Discussion Panels, 2001 October (Box 41, Folder 491)
  - LCW - Partnership Meeting, 2001 November 8 (Box 41, Folder 492)
  - Center for Democracy and Citizenship - Reports and Press Materials, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 493)
  - Innovations in American Government: Creative Solutions to Public Concerns, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 494)
  - Collaborations that Count: Intermediaries Budget FY 2002 - FY 2005, 2001 November 7 (Box 41, Folder 495)
  - Civic Talk to Civic Action: Taking Stock of Democratic Renewal, Democracy and Citizenship Program, Aspen, Colorado, 1999 April 4-7 (Box 41, Folder 496)
  - Program Officer Memo - Biographic Summary of Michael Lipsky, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 497)
  - National Institute of Governmental Purchasing - Rick Grimm, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 498)
  - Rethinking the Public Sector Workforce for the Twenty First Century, Steven Kelman, Harvard University, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 499)
  - Innovation Partnership (Formerly Metropolitan Portland Fund for Civic Innovation) - Ruth Elizabeth Scott, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 500)
  - Institute for America's Future - Social Security - Roger Hickey, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 501)
  - Clippings, Correspondence, and Reports - April, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 502)
  - Meeting Preparation Materials, 2001 February (Box 42, Folder 503)
  - Progressive Leadership Alliance of Nevada (PLAN) - Recent Materials, 1999-2001 (Box 42, Folder 504)
  - Media Coverage for Innovations Finalists, Winners, and Events, 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 505-507)
  - Media Plan for Partnership For Trust in Government Launch, 1997 October (Box 42, Folder 508)
  - Introduction to Grantmakers Income Security Task Force (GIST) - Invitation to Conference - Anne N. Shkuda, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 509)
  - International Seminar on Innovation and Improving Government Performance, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 510)
  - Innovations 1994 (Box 42, Folder 511)
  - Innovations 1995 Application (Box 42, Folder 512)
  - Innovations 1995: Jane Dunne Report (Box 42, Folder 513)
  - Innovations 1996 - Replication (Box 43, Folder 514)
  - Innovations 1996 - Strategic Alliances (Box 43, Folder 515)
  - Innovations 1996 - Update on Innovations, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 516)
  - Harvard University, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 517)
  - Innovations in the News, 1996 December (Box 43, Folder 518)
  - Commission on Civil Society, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 519)
  - Innovations Press Clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 43, Folder 520)
  - Grantmakers Forum Conference - Berkeley, California, 1999 November 6-9 (Box 43, Folder 521)
  - Wisconsin Council on Children and Families, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 522)
  - Pennsylvania Partnership for Children, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 523)
  - Rhode Island Kids Count, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 524)
  - United Vision for Idaho, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 525)
  - Voices for Children in Nebraska, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 526)
  - Oregon Center for Public Policy, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 527)
  - Status Sheet - Partner Communications Initiative, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 528)
  - Communications Initiative - Parade Magazine Citizen Nominated Award for Excellence in Government - Concept Statement, undated (Box 44, Folder 529)
  - Communications Initiative - American Perspectives, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 530)
  - Communications Initiative - Updates, 1997 January 27 (Box 44, Folder 531)
  - Communications Initiative - AFL/CIO, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 532)
  - Communications Initiative - Restoring the Balance (Martin/Glantz), undated (Box 44, Folder 533)
  - Communications Initiative - American Association of Museums - Edward Able, Jr., 1996 (Box 44, Folder 534)
  - Communications Initiative - American Medical Association, Chicago, Illinois, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 535)
  - Communications Initiative - American Youth Museum - Janet Rice Elman, 1996-1999 (Box 44, Folder 536)
  - Communications Initiative - Catholic Charities - Sharon Daly, undated (Box 44, Folder 537)
  - Communications Initiative - Edison International, 1995-1997 (Box 44, Folder 538)
  - Communications Initiative - GEICO - Ron Loy, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 539)
  - National Council of Nonprofit Associations (NCNA), 1996 (Box 44, Folder 540)
  - State Fiscal Analysis Initiative - Tennessee, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 541-542)
  - China Trip File, 1999 May 14-26 (Box 45, Folder 543)
  - New Leaders for a Changing World - Proposals, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 544-549, Box 46, Folder 550-551)
    MDC, Inc., The Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service, The Common Enterprise
    Fetzer Institute and Center for Assessment and Policy Development
    Public/Private Ventures
    Advocacy Institute
    Southern Regional Council
  - State Fiscal Analysis Initiative - Press Release, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 552)
  - State Fiscal Analysis Initiative - Request for Information, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 553)
  - State Fiscal Analysis Initiative - Responses to Inquiries, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 554)
  - History of State Fiscal Analysis Initiative Notes, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 555)
  - State Fiscal Analysis Initiative Project - Consultants, 1992-1994 (Box 46, Folder 556)
  - State Fiscal Analysis Initiative - Mailings, 1994-1995 (Box 46, Folder 557)
  - Maryland - Attachments from Nonprofits, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 558)
  - Maryland Association of Nonprofit Organizations - Grant Application for State Fiscal Analysis Initiative, 1997 April 23 (Box 46, Folder 559)
  - Partnership File - Good Housekeeping - Correspondence with Ellen Levine and Lisa Berenson, 1996-1998 (Box 46, Folder 560)
    Includes July 1998 and November 1996 copies of Good Housekeeping
  - Partnership File - Good Housekeeping Women in Government Award, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 561)
    Includes July 1998 edition of Good Housekeeping
  - Partnership File - Museum of Television and Radio, 1998-1999 (Box 47, Folder 562)
  - Partnership File - TV Content Analysis Project, 1997-1998 (Box 47, Folder 563)
  - Minnesota Council of Nonprofits, 1995-1997 (Box 47, Folder 564)
  - Innovations in American Government - Meeting with Pat McGinnis of The Council for Excellence in Government, and Joe Gleason, Washington, D.C., 1997 May 23 (Box 47, Folder 565)
  - Michigan Community Service Commission Meeting, Midland, Michigan, 1997 May 15-17 (Box 47, Folder 566)
  - Harvard University Spring Symposium - Why Has Confidence in Government Declined?, 1997 May 9-10 (Box 47, Folder 567)
  - Meeting on Devolution with Carolyn Lukensmeyer, 1997 April 1 (Box 47, Folder 568)
  - Meeting with Ester Fuchs and Phil Thompson, 1997 April 11 (Box 47, Folder 569)
  - Local Governance Grantee Meeting Mexico, 1996 June 12-15 (Box 47, Folder 570)
  - Michael Lipsky's Past Trips, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 571)
  - Florence Bonner Meeting - Institute for Women's Policy Research, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 572)
  - Gregg Petersmeyer Meeting - Youth Service America, 1997 March 13 (Box 47, Folder 573)
  - Medical Care for Children Partnership - Advisory Council Retreat, Fairfax, Virginia, 1996 October 26 (Box 47, Folder 574)
  - Meeting with Joe Gleason, Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 47, Folder 575)
  - Meeting - Lizzy Flanagan - Youth on Board, 1997 March 13 (Box 47, Folder 576)
  - Design Cities Action Clinic, Washington, D.C., 1996 September 20 (Box 48, Folder 577)
  - Dinner at Fall Conference for Community Foundations, San Diego, California, 1996 September 10 (Box 48, Folder 578)
  - Annual Meeting of the American Political Science Association (APSA), San Francisco, California, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 579)
  - Grantmakers Income Security Task Force (GIST) Summer Meeting, Dayton, Ohio, 1996 July (Box 48, Folder 580)
  - Oregon Progress Board - Governance Benchmarking Meeting, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 581)
  - Hilton Foundation - Conrad N. Hilton Humanitarian Prize, Los Angeles, California, 1996 June 20 (Box 48, Folder 582)
  - 20th Century Fund, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 583)
  - Kettering Foundation, Dayton, Ohio, 1996 May 28-29 (Box 48, Folder 584)
  - Ford Positive Business Climates Project, Washington, D.C., 1996 April 25 (Box 48, Folder 585)
  - Council on Foundations, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 586)
  - National Youth Service Day, Washington, D.C., 1996 April 23 (Box 48, Folder 587)
  - Association for Public Policy Analysis and Management, Curriculum Response to the Changing Policy Landscape, Washington, D.C., 1996 March 29-30 (Box 48, Folder 588)
  - Joint Center for Political and Economic Research Annual Dinner, 1996 March 19 (Box 48, Folder 589)
  - National Commission on State and Local Public Service - Meeting on State Capacity and Devolution, Washington D.C., 1996 January 18-19 (Box 48, Folder 590)
  - Key Contacts for Kids Count, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 591)
  - Thank You Letters to Consultants, 1993 August (Box 48, Folder 592)
  - Annie E. Casey Foundation, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 593)
  - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1992-1994 (Box 48, Folder 594)
  - Annual Reports - Woods Charitable Fund and The Fund for New Jersey, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 595)
  - Reactions to State Fiscal Project, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 596)
  - State Fiscal Analysis Initiative Newsletters, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 597)
  - IBM Corporation - Ken Thornton Meeting, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 598)
  - National Service - League of Women Voters, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 599)
  - National Service - MTV Networks - Helen Boehm, 1996-1998 (Box 48, Folder 600)
  - National Service - National Cable Television Association - Decker Anstrom, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 601)
  - National Service - National Audubon Society - John Flicker, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 602)
  - National Service - National Council of Churches of Christ - Rich Killmer and Eileen Lindner, 1997-1998 (Box 49, Folder 603)
  - National Service - National Resources Defense Council - John Adams and Frances Beinecke, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 604)
  - National Service - Scholastic News and Junior Scholastic, 1998 February 9 (Box 49, Folder 605)
  - National Service - Tenneco - Arthur House, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 606)
  - National Service - Union of American Hebrew Congregations - Leonard Fein, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 607)
  - National Service - United Negro College Fund - Alan Kirschner, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 608)
  - National Service - Urban League - Hugh Price, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 609)
  - National Service - World Wildlife Fund - Katherine Fuller, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 610)
  - National Service - YWCA of the USA - Jo Uehara, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 611)
  - The Council for Excellence in Government - Attitudes for Government, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 612)
  - China, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 613)
  - Philippines, 2000-2001 (Box 49, Folder 614)
  - Nigeria, undated (Box 49, Folder 615)
  - Brazil, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 616)
  - Chile, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 617)
  - Collaborations that Count (CTC), 2002 (Box 49, Folder 618)
  - State Strategies Fund Survey, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 619)
  - Homeland Security, 2001 December (Box 49, Folder 620)
  - State Fiscal Analysis Desk File, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 621)
  - Harvard Desk File, undated (Box 49, Folder 622)
  - Mike Edwards, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 623)
  - Budget and Finance Information Network (BFAN) Program Learning Group, 1998-2000 (Box 49, Folder 624)
  - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities International Project, 1998-1999 (Box 49, Folder 625)
  - International Budget Project, 2001-2003 (Box 50, Folder 626)
  - Making Democracy Work: A Report to the Ford Foundation, Governance and Civil Society Program, Miles Rapoport, 2001 August (Box 50, Folder 627)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives - Proposal - Evaluation Project, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 628)
  - Honoring Nations, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 629)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives - Report and Proposal, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 630)
  - Forum on Democracy and Trade, Miles Rapoport, 2002-2003 (Box 50, Folder 631)
  - Gary Delgado - Applied Research Center Drafts, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 632)
  - Miles Rapaport Reports, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 633)
  - Protecting Americans Against Markets: How Market Alternatives Enlarge Government Responsibility and Underinvest in Government Capacity, Lawrence Brown - Draft, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 634)
  - Idaho Fund, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 635)
  - Fannie Mae Foundation, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 636)
  - Memo Regarding Rinku Sen's Draft Report - Study of National Intermediaries Overview and Purpose, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 637)
  - Review Drafts - Maine Center for Economic Policy and California Budget Project, undated (Box 50, Folder 638)
  - International Budget Project - San Francisco Breakfast, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 639)
  - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities - Funding Contacts, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 640)
  - Forum on Democracy and Trade, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 641)
  - National Constitution Center, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 642)
  - Isaac Shapiro, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 643)
  - Transparency International, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 644)
  - Africa Budget Project, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 645)
  - Center for Economic and Policy Research, Mark Weisbrot, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 646)
  - Harrison Institute for Public Law, Georgetown University Law Center, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 647)
  - State Fiscal Analysis Initiative Assets Grants, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 648)
  - Kennedy School - Network for Innovative Government, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 649)
  - United for a Fair Economy, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 650)
  - L.A. Alliance for a New Economy, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 651)
  - Susan Stroud - National Service, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 652)
  - Los Angeles Alliance for a New Economy (LAANE) California Project, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 653)
  - Worker Retention Ordinance, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 654)
  - Center for Public Leadership - David Gergan, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 655)
  - Center for Governmental Studies, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 656)
  - Transparency International, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 657)
  - The Corruption Fighters' Tool Kit: Civil Society Experiences and Emerging Strategies, 2001 October (Box 51, Folder 657)
  - Government Accountability Project, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 658)
  - Study of National Intermediaries, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 659)
  - Partnership for Public Service, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 660)
  - OMG Center - Tom Burns, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 661)
  - Washington Association of Churches and Chris Haugen, 2001 October (Box 52, Folder 662)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting - Reports, 2002 September (Box 52, Folder 663)
  - Women's Funding Movement Report, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 664)
  - State Fiscal Analysis Initiative (SFAI) - Reports, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 665)
  - Issues and Media in the Presidential Elections, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 666)
  - Latino Policy Centers, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 667)
  - New York City Fiscal Crisis, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 668)
  - Partnership For Trust in Government, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 669)
  - Labor-Management Cooperation Materials, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 670)
  - Grantmakers' Income Security Task Force (GIST), 1993-1994 (Box 52, Folder 671)
  - Grantmakers' Income Security Task Force (GIST) Meeting, 1992 July 20 (Box 52, Folder 672)
  - David Arnold Interoffice Memos, 1991-1992 (Box 53, Folder 673)
  - Campaign Finance, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 674)
  - The Common Good: Social Welfare and the American Future, 1991-1992 (Box 53, Folder 675)
    Meeting with religious leaders about the Common Good:
    William E. Lesher, Dennis Schnurr, Dr. Joan Campbell, and Rabbi Mark Tannenbaum
    Ford staff who attended: Shepard Forman, Michael Lipsky, and Andrea Taylor
  - Texas Conference – Texas Grantees, 1997 June 10 (Box 53, Folder 676)
  - Texas Conference on Devolution - Ford Foundation Grantees - Working Files, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 677)
    Devolution: An Interactive Forum Concerning the Impact on Texas Communities: A Conference for Ford Foundation Grantees
  - Board of Trustees Meeting - National and Youth Community Service Programs, 1994 March 23 (Box 53, Folder 678)
  - Changing Domestic Priorities II Memo - New Directions in a National Policy, 1993-1994 (Box 53, Folder 679)
  - Improving Governance in U.S. - Overview of Goals and Objectives, 1991-1992 (Box 54, Folder 680)
  - Final Application Package for State Fiscal Analysis Initiative (SFAI) Operational Grants, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 681)
  - Robert Greenstein, Executive Director of Center on Budget and Policy Priorities, 1991-1993 (Box 54, Folder 682)
  - Cross Reference Sheet - "The Peace and Social Justice Program: Goals, Expected Outcomes, and Results," A Report to the Ford Foundation, Judith Tendler, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 683)
  - Consultant: Tobi Walker - Desk File, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 684)
  - Workshop on Political Participation, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 685)
  - Inter-regional Project on Local Democracy, 1992-1993 (Box 54, Folder 686)
  - National Service, 1997 October (Box 54, Folder 687)
  - Correspondence and Notes, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 688)
    Correspondence and notes from Lipsky's time as temporary Assistant in the Public Affairs Program at the Ford Foundation in 1965
  - Desk File: Current Situation in the States - Budget, Fiscal Issues, 2001-2002 (Box 54, Folder 689)
  - Devolution, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 690)
  - Ford Foundation Diversity and Equal Opportunity Policy, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 691)
  - Globalvision - Galbraith Project, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 692)
  - Grantseeker's Checklist, undated (Box 54, Folder 693)
  - International Budget Project and Public Finance Files, 1995-1997 (Box 54, Folder 694)